Ai

Aisha Amate

+63 966 400 9309 Alhime1225@gmail.com

Quezon City

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

My interest in software development started when it was introduced to me in high school after which it turned into a growing passion; learning new technology and exploring the field of IT has been really fulfilling and really enjoyable.

WORK HISTORY

May 2020 - May 2022

Individual Trader and Fund Manager, MFF

- Market Analysis (Technical and Fundamental)
- Identifying patterns
- Stock forecasting

May 2018 - May 2020

Consultant, QA Consulting

- Using Maven projects and test suite using Junit
- Using selenium and cucumber alongside Junit, using various concepts such as; data driven testing (DDT), test driven development (TDD) and behavioural driven development (BDD)
- DDT concept is used with selenium to automatedly test websites, BDD was used to create user stories using Cucumber

September 2018 - September 2019

QA Engineer, NETBuilder

- Involves reviewing Business requirements, IT Design documents and preparing Test Plans which involve various Test Cases for all assigned modules/projects
- Created Test plan & Script, Defect Management Templates; Created Initial test plan and developed test cases and test scripts manually
- Developed a Defects Tracking Log for the SharePoint Site to track defects while testing
- Involved in UAT testing, SIT Testing, Regression Testing and Functional testing
- Prepared & published Daily & Weekly QA status reports
- Actively participated in all QA and testing activities during Dev, FT, UAT and PROD SDLC (Software Development lifecycle)
- Having hands on experience in device testing mobile and tablet device testing
- Involved in cross browsing testing (compatibility testing) of the application on various browsers to ensure it functions

• Having hands on experience in component testing, integration testing and regression testing

EDUCATION

June 2018

Bachelor of Science, Computing With Games Development **University of Greenwich**, Old Royal Naval College, Park Row, London SE10 9LS

CERTIFICATIONS

Level 2 Creating a Business Start-Up, 2022 Level 2 Customer Service in NCFE, 2022 BCS Certificate in ISTQB Foundations, 2018 Oracle Leadership 2016